fuzzys.com 2013-04-21

# Fuzzys - Stuff to make you laugh | Privacy Policy

Users’ privacy is very important to fuzzys.com

### How Do We Collect Information?

Users will never be implicitly added to any marketing lists.  The User has the right to opt-in or opt-out at any time.

### What Information Do We Collect?

fuzzys.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Fuzzys may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Website.

### How We Use Information

fuzzys.com may use personally identifiable information collected through our web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by fuzzys.com and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with us. fuzzys.com may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of fuzzys.com.

### Disclosure of Information

fuzzys.com will not disclose information collected from Users to third parties. However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of fuzzys.com’s business.

### Maintenance of Information

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures.

### Questions

Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to darren@fuzzys.com
